

PALAK VYAS

Mobile No:- +91-8357976308

Linkedin profile:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/palak-vyas-770a45234/

Email:- pvvyas638@gmail.com

Objective:-

To be a part of an Organization that provides an atmosphere of mutual growth and benefits, where I can show my talent and potential in order to benefit my organization and during work in organization learn about new technologies that help me to achieve my goal.

Profile Summary:-

HR Professional with 9month of experience in Recruitment, Training and Development, conflict resolution, Employee records management, HR Proficiency in recruitment process entailing resume generation, screening and short-listing with appropriate compensation. Merit of providing prompt resolution of employee grievances to maintain cordial management-employee relations. Successful at motivating staff through clear communication and outstanding organizational skills.

Personal Strength:-

Good Communication skill in English and Hindi both verbal and written, responsible, self-directed, hardworking, creative, bold and self-motivated to work independently or in team and dedicated and willingness to learn new technical skill.

HR Skills:-

- -Recruitment
- -Sourcing and Shortlisting
- Training & Development
- -MIS Report

- Employee Relations / Welfare
- Talent Pool Selection
- -Employee Engagement
- Employee Relation

Academic & Professional Profile:-

Qualification:-

- MBA (HR, Finance) (2019-2021), from Astral Institute of Technology & Research, Indore. with 75%
- B.sc Computer Sci, (2016-2019), from PMB Gujarati Science College with 67% •
- •12th from Padmaja higher secondary school (M.P. Board) with 81.8%.
- •10th from Padmaja higher secondary (M.P. Board) with 79%.

Experience:-

·Working experience from :-

=>SSAM SOFTWARES-(22aug2022 -13apr2023)

Role and Responsibilities:-

- 1)Responsible for end to end recruitment process: i.e. sourcing, screening, joining, formalities, on boarding, induction,& orientation.
- 2) Familier from job portals like linkedin, indeed and other job portals.
- 3)Preparing and make job description as per requirement of organisation.
- 4) Maintain employee records and engagement.
- 5) Making attendance sheet , maintaining leave records.
- 6)Collaborate with manager to identify future hiring need
- 7)Conducting preliminary interviews with the candidates and shortlisting candidates for the final interview with the company.

- 8)Preparing and submitting all relevant letter/documents/ certifications as per the requirements in consultation with the management.
- 9)Build network and contacts to source candidates as per requirements.

=>MACTOSYS SOFTWARES -(17april2023 -15july2023)

Role and Responsibilities:-

- 1)Responsible for end to end recruitment process: i.e. sourcing, screening, joining, formalities, on boarding, induction,& orientation.
- 2) Familier from job portals like linkedin, indeed and other job portals.
- 3)Preparing and make job description as per requirement of organisation.
- 4)Collaborate with HR and the manager to identify future hiring need.
- 5)Conducting interviews /initial screening of the candidates and shortlisting candidates for the final interview with the company.
- 6)Preparing and submitting all relevant letter/documents/ certifications as per the requirements in consultation with the management.
- 7)Build network and connection to company page and group for sourcing candidates as per requirements.

Computer Skills:-

- Specialty Typing Speed up to 20-25wpm
- MS-Office Word, MS-Excel, etc.

Area of Interest:-

• Human Resource Management.

Extracurricular Activity:-

• Participated in Dance Competition.

• Speech Debate Competition

Personal Profile:-

Hobbies & Interest : - Music, Dancing, Travelling, Photography

Date of Birth: - 19-Aug-1998

Nationality: - Indian

Language Known: - English and Hindi

Mother Tongue : - Hindi

Father's Name: - Mr. Om Prakash Vyas

Mother's Name: - Mrs. Sulekha Vyas

Contact Address : - 348 Suncity-2 ,Dewas (M.P.)

I hereby declare that the information given above is true to the best of my knowledge & belief.

Date:

Palak Vyas